question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Adolf Hitler was born in Australia. ",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Musicals &amp; Theatres",
     "question": "IMAX stands for Image Maximum.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Tokyo is the capital of Japan.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "History",
     "question": "The United States Department of Homeland Security was formed in response to the September 11th attacks.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Until Dawn, both characters Sam and Mike cannot be killed under any means until the final chapter of the game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
